(gentle bouncy music)
♪ I've never seen a diamond in the flesh ♪
♪ I cut my teeth on wedding
rings in the movies ♪
♪ And I'm not proud of my address ♪
♪ In a torn up town, no postcode envy ♪
♪ But every song's like ♪
♪ Gold teeth, Grey Goose,
trippin' in the bathroom ♪
♪ Bloodstains, ball gowns,
trashin' the hotel room ♪
♪ We don't care ♪
♪ We're driving Cadillacs in our dreams ♪
♪ But everybody's like ♪
♪ Cristal, Maybach,
diamonds on your timepiece ♪
♪ Jet planes, islands,
tigers on a gold leash ♪
♪ We don't care ♪
♪ We aren't caught up
in your love affair ♪
♪ And we'll never be royals ♪
♪ It don't run in our blood ♪
♪ That kind of luxe just ain't for us ♪
♪ We crave a different kind of buzz ♪
♪ Let me be your ruler ♪
♪ You can call me queen bee ♪
♪ And baby, I'll rule ♪
♪ Let me live that fantasy ♪
♪ My friends and I,
we've cracked the code ♪
♪ We count our dollars on
the train to the party ♪
♪ And everyone who knows us knows ♪
♪ That we're fine with this,
we didn't come from money ♪
♪ But every song's like ♪
♪ Gold teeth, Grey Goose,
trippin' in the bathroom ♪
♪ Bloodstains, ball gowns,
trashin' the hotel room ♪
♪ We don't care ♪
♪ We're driving Cadillacs in our dreams ♪
♪ But everybody's like ♪
♪ Cristal, Maybach,
diamonds on your timepiece ♪
♪ Jet planes, islands,
tigers on a gold leash ♪
♪ We don't care ♪
♪ We aren't caught up
in your love affair ♪
♪ And we'll never be royals ♪
♪ It don't run in our blood ♪
♪ That kind of luxe just ain't for us ♪
♪ We crave a different kind of buzz ♪
♪ Let me be your ruler ♪
♪ You can call me queen bee ♪
♪ And baby, I'll rule ♪
♪ Let me live that fantasy ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We're bigger than we ever dreamed ♪
♪ And I'm in love with being queen ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Life is great without a care ♪
♪ We aren't caught up
in your love affair ♪
♪ And we'll never be royals ♪
♪ It don't run in our blood ♪
♪ That kind of luxe just ain't for us ♪
♪ We crave a different kind of buzz ♪
♪ Let me be your ruler ♪
♪ You can call me queen bee ♪
♪ And baby, I'll rule ♪
♪ Let me live that fantasy ♪